Guide to the Sigma Xi, The Scientific Research Society Records
Sigma Xi, The Scientific Research Society Records
- Administrative Records, 1937-2002; 1937 2002; 98.25 linear feet
  - Prominent Members
    - Jackson, C. Ian
      - Correspondence, 19-23 Jan. 1987 (Box 1.157, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence, 26-30 Jan. 1987 (Box 1.157, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence, 2-6 Feb. 1987 (Box 1.157, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence, 9-13 Feb. 1987 (Box 1.157, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence, 16-20 Feb. 1987 (Box 1.157, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence, 23-27 Feb. 1987 (Box 1.157, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence, 2-20 Mar. 1987 (Box 1.157, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence, 23 Mar. - 3 Apr. 1987 (Box 1.157, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence, 6-10 Apr. 1987 (Box 1.157, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence, 13-17 Apr. 1987 (Box 1.157, Folder 22)
      - Correspondence, 20 Apr. - 1 May 1987 (Box 1.157, Folder 23)
      - Correspondence, 4-8 May 1987 (Box 1.158, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, 11-15 May 1987 (Box 1.158, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, 18-22 May 1987 (Box 1.158, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, 25-29 May 1987 (Box 1.158, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, 30 May - 5 Jun. 1987 (Box 1.158, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, 8-12 Jun. 1987 (Box 1.158, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, 15-19 Jun. 1987 (Box 1.158, Folder 7)
      - Itineraries, 1986 (Box 1.158, Folder 8)
      - Itineraries, 1986 (Box 1.158, Folder 9)
      - Itineraries, 1986-1987 (Box 1.158, Folder 10)
      - Itineraries, 1987 (Box 1.158, Folder 11)
      - Itineraries, 1987-1988 (Box 1.158, Folder 12)
      - Itineraries, 1987-1988 (Box 1.158, Folder 13)
      - Resignation, 1987 (Box 1.158, Folder 14)
      - Meeting: Annual Meeting, 1986 (Box 1.192, Folder 7)
      - Meeting: Annual Meeting, 1986 (Box 1.192, Folder 8)
      - Trip Reports, 1987 (Box 1.158, Folder 15)
    - Malone, Thomas F.
      - Advisory Council, 1996 (Halfbox 1.193, Folder 1)
      - Avila Workshop, 1993 (Box 1.158, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 1.158, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 1.158, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 1.159, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 1.159, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 1.159, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 1.159, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 1.159, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 1.159, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, Jan. 1987 (Box 1.159, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, Feb. 1987 (Box 1.159, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, Mar. 1987 (Box 1.159, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, Apr. 1987 (Box 1.159, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, May 1987 (Box 1.159, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, Jun. 1987 (Box 1.159, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, Jul. 1987 (Box 1.159, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence, Aug. 1987 (Box 1.159, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence, Dec. 1987 (Box 1.159, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 1.159, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 1.159, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 1.159, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 1.159, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence, Jan. 1988 (Box 1.159, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence, Feb. 1988 (Box 1.159, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence, Mar. 1988 (Box 1.159, Folder 22)
      - Correspondence, Apr. 1988 (Box 1.159, Folder 23)
      - Correspondence, May 1988 (Box 1.16, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, Jun. 1988 (Box 1.16, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, Jul. 1988 (Box 1.16, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, Aug. 1988 (Box 1.16, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, Sep. 1988 (Box 1.16, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, Oct. 1988 (Box 1.16, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, Nov. 1988 (Box 1.16, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, Dec. 1988 (Box 1.16, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, 1 Dec. 1988 - 20 Apr. 1989 (Box 1.16, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, Jan. 1989 (Box 1.16, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, Feb. 1989 (Box 1.16, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, Mar. 1989 (Box 1.16, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, Apr. 1989 (Box 1.16, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence, 26 Apr. - 17 Jul. 1989 (Box 1.16, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence, Jun. 1989 (Box 1.16, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence, Jul. 1989 (Box 1.16, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence, 24 Jul. 1989 - 5 Oct. 1993 (Box 1.16, Folder 17)
      - Documents on Nuclear Warfare, 1982 (Box 1.16, Folder 18)
      - General, 1988-1995 (Box 1.16, Folder 19)
      - Informal Consultative Group (White paper), 1996 (Halfbox 1.193, Folder 2)
      - Meeting: Global Array of Nested Networks, 18 Jan. 1994 (Box 1.16, Folder 20)
      - Meetings: Research Triangle Sigma Xi, 1995-1996 (Halfbox 1.193, Folder 3)
      - Miscellaneous Meetings, 1995-1996 (Box 1.16, Folder 21)
      - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges White Paper, 1994 (Box 1.161, Folder 1)
      - Proposals, 1993 (Box 1.161, Folder 2)
      - Visualization Technologies in Environmental Curricula Proposal, 1993-1995 (Box 1.161, Folder 3)
      - Workshop on International Networks, 23-25 Aug. 1983 (Box 1.161, Folder 4)
    - McNamara, Thomas F.
      - Correspondence, 1985-1987 (Halfbox 1.193, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, 23 Jun. - 9 Jul. 1987 (Box 1.161, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, 10-31 Jul. 1987 (Box 1.161, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, 1-5 Aug. 1987 (Box 1.161, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, 6-26 Aug. 1987 (Box 1.161, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, 27-31 Aug. 1987 (Box 1.161, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, Sep. 1987 (Box 1.161, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, Oct. 1987 (Box 1.161, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, Nov. 1987 (Box 1.161, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, 1-11 Dec. 1987 (Box 1.161, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence, 14-31 Dec. 1987 (Box 1.161, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence, Jan. 1988 (Box 1.161, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence, 1-5 Feb. 1988 (Box 1.161, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence, 6-16 Feb. 1988 (Box 1.161, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence, 17-29 Feb. 1988 (Box 1.161, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence, 1-7 Mar. 1988 (Box 1.162, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, 8-23 Mar. 1988 (Box 1.162, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, 24-30 Mar. 1988 (Box 1.162, Folder 3)
    - Munson, Harriet L.
      - Chronologic Files, Jan. - Feb. 1983 (Box 1.162, Folder 4)
      - Chronologic Files, Mar. 1983 (Box 1.162, Folder 5)
      - Chronologic Files, Apr. 1983 (Box 1.162, Folder 6)
      - Chronologic Files, May 1983 (Box 1.162, Folder 7)
      - Chronologic Files, Jun. - Jul. 1983 (Box 1.162, Folder 8)
      - Chronologic Files, Jul. - Dec. 1983 (Box 1.162, Folder 9)
    - Poziomek, Edward J.
      - Correspondence, Apr. 1988 (Box 1.163, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, May 1988 (Box 1.163, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, Jun. 1988 (Box 1.163, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, Jul. 1988 (Box 1.163, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, Aug. 1988 (Box 1.163, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, Sep. 1988 (Box 1.163, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, Oct. 1988 (Box 1.163, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, Nov. 1988 (Box 1.163, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, Dec. 1988 (Box 1.163, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, Jan. 1989 (Box 1.163, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, Feb. 1989 (Box 1.163, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, Mar. 1989 (Box 1.164, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, Apr. 1989 (Box 1.164, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, May 1989 (Halfbox 1.164, Folder 3)
      - Itineraries, 1988 (Box 1.193, Folder 5)
      - "The Potential Role of Senior and Retired Members in Sigma Xi Activities", 20 Feb. 1989 (Box 1.164, Folder 4)
- Committee Records, 1952-2003; 1952 2003; 101.5 linear feet
  This series contains records from some of the committees which operate under the leadership of the Board of Directors of Sigma Xi. This series does not contain records from all of Sigma Xi's committees, and is mostly limited to a few of the more prominent committees: the Committee on Grants-In-Aid of Research and the Committees on Lectureships; Membership; Qualifications; and Science, Math, and Engineering. The material found in this series consists primarily of correspondence and information pertaining to meetings each of the committees held throughout the year, and is arranged alphabetically, then chronologically therein.
  Records of grants funded by the Committee on Grants-In-Aid of Research are arranged according to the month the grant application was received by Sigma Xi. The grant applications present reflect a ten percent sample of all applications received in each calander year; only applications which were funded by Sigma Xi have been kept.
  Materials are arranged alphabetically by name of the committee. Records of the Executive Committee can be found in Series 1, Administrative Records.
  - Committee on Audit Review
    - General, 1991-1993 (Box 2.001, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Awards
    - 21st Century Award, 1992 (Box 2.001, Folder 2)
    - Certificate of Excellence Award, 1992 (Box 2.001, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 2.001, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 19 Apr. 1991 (Box 2.001, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Nov. 1991 (Box 2.001, Folder 6)
    - Conference Call, 11 Jan. 1995 (Box 2.001, Folder 7)
    - General, 1991-1993 (Box 2.001, Folder 8)
    - General, 1991-1993 (Box 2.001, Folder 9)
    - McGovern Award, 1983-1994 (Box 2.001, Folder 10)
    - Proctor Prize Award, 1992 (Box 2.001, Folder 11)
  - Building Committee
    - Conference Call, 1990-1993 (Box 2.001, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 7 Jan. 1991 (Box 2.001, Folder 13)
  - Committees, Miscellaneous
    - Ad Hoc Committee on the Future Role of Sigma Xi in Public Understanding, 1975 (Box 2.16, Folder 6)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on the Future Role of Sigma Xi in Public Understanding, 1975-1976 (Box 2.16, Folder 7)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on the Future Role of Sigma Xi in Public Understanding, 1976-1977 (Box 2.16, Folder 8)
    - Ad Hoc Committee to Study the Executive Committee, 1977 (Box 2.16, Folder 9)
    - Committee Chairs, 1990-1992 (Box 2.001, Folder 14)
    - Committee Chairs Conference Calls, 10 Dec. 1990 (Box 2.161, Folder 2)
    - Committee Chairs Conference Call, 23 Sept. 1991 (Box 2.161, Folder 3)
    - Committee Chairs: Meeting, 28 Feb. 1990 (Box 2.002, Folder 3)
    - Committee Conference Call Questionnaire, 20 Aug. 1990 (Box 2.001, Folder 15)
    - Committee Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Halfbox 2.192, Folder 5)
    - Committees: General, 1991-1992 (Box 2.001, Folder 16)
    - Committee Letters and Responses, 1994-1995 (Box 2.001, Folder 17)
    - Committee Letters and Responses, 1994-1995 (Box 2.002, Folder 1)
    - Committee Letters and Responses, 1994-1995 (Box 2.002, Folder 2)
    - Committee Members' Information, 1987-1994 (Halfbox 2.192, Folder 6)
    - Committee Responses, 1993-1994 (Box 2.002, Folder 4)
    - Conference Calls, 1990 (Box 2.161, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Jan. - Mar. 1985 (Box 2.002, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Apr. 1985 (Box 2.002, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, May - Jul. 1985 (Box 2.002, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Aug. - Dec. 1985 (Box 2.002, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Jan. - Apr. 1986 (Box 2.003, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, May - Jun. 1986 (Box 2.003, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Jul. - Dec. 1986 (Box 2.003, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Jan. - Apr. 1987 (Box 2.003, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, May - Jun. 1987 (Box 2.003, Folder 5)
    - Operating Divisions and Committee Chairs Meeting, 17-18 Mar. 1990 (Box 2.161, Folder 4)
    - Sigma Xi - The Scientific Research Society of America Joint Committee, 1952 (Box 2.161, Folder 5)
    - Sigma Xi - The Scientific Research Society of America Joint Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 2.161, Folder 6)
    - Sigma Xi - The Scientific Research Society of America Joint Committee, 1970-1972 (Box 2.161, Folder 7)
    - Sigma Xi - The Scientific Research Society of America Joint Committee, 1973 (Box 2.161, Folder 8)
  - Commonwealth Awards Committee
    - Correspondence, 29 Apr. 1991 (Box 2.003, Folder 6)
    - General Information, 1987 (Box 2.003, Folder 7)
    - General, 1987-1990 (Box 2.161, Folder 9)
    - General, 1991 (Box 2.003, Folder 8)
    - General, 1991 (Box 2.003, Folder 9)
    - General, 1992 (Box 2.004, Folder 1)
    - General, 1992 (Box 2.004, Folder 2)
    - General, 1993 (Box 2.004, Folder 3)
    - General, 1993 (Box 2.004, Folder 4)
    - General, 1994 (Box 2.004, Folder 5)
    - General, undated (Box 2.161, Folder 10)
    - Recipients, 1980-1981 (Box 2.004, Folder 6)
    - Recipients, 1982 (Box 2.004, Folder 7)
    - Recipients, 1986 (Box 2.004, Folder 8)
    - Recipients, 1987 (Box 2.005, Folder 1)
    - Recipients in Invention, 1983 (Box 2.005, Folder 2)
    - Recipients in Science, 1983 (Box 2.005, Folder 3)
    - Recipients in Science and Invention, 1984 (Box 2.005, Folder 4)
    - Recipients in Science and Invention, 1985 (Box 2.005, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Development
    - Committee Response, 1992 (Box 2.005, Folder 6)
    - Committee Service, 1993-1994 (Box 2.005, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 23-25 Sep. 1988 (Box 2.005, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 2-3 Mar. 1990 (Box 2.005, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 2 Feb. 1991 (Box 2.005, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 2.005, Folder 11)
    - General, 1988 (Box 2.161, Folder 11)
    - Meeting, 15 Nov. 1992 (Box 2.005, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Diversity
    - Ford Foundation Fellows, 1996-1998 (Box 2.005, Folder 13)
    - General, 1992-1993 (Box 2.005, Folder 14)
    - General, 1994 (Box 2.005, Folder 15)
    - General, 1995 (Box 2.005, Folder 16)
    - General, 1995 (Box 2.005, Folder 17)
    - General, 1995 (Box 2.006, Folder 1)
    - General, 1996 (Box 2.006, Folder 2)
    - General, 1996 (Box 2.006, Folder 3)
    - General, 1996 (Box 2.006, Folder 4)
    - General, 1997 (Box 2.006, Folder 5)
    - General, 1997 (Box 2.006, Folder 6)
    - General, 1997 (Box 2.007, Folder 1)
    - General, 1998 (Box 2.007, Folder 2)
    - General, 1998 (Box 2.007, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, 12-14 Jan. 2001 (Box 2.007, Folder 4)
    - Retreat, Aug. 1995 (Box 2.007, Folder 5)
    - Sourcebook, 1995 (Box 2.007, Folder 6)
    - Sourcebook, 1999 (Box 2.007, Folder 7)
    - Workshop, 22 Nov. 1991 (Box 2.161, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Ethics
    - General, 1989-1992 (Box 2.008, Folder 1)
    - General, 1989-1992 (Box 2.008, Folder 2)
    - General, 1991-1992 (Box 2.008, Folder 3)
    - General, 1994 (Box 2.008, Folder 4)
  - Finance Committee
    - Audit Report, 1964 (Box 2.161, Folder 13)
    - Audit Review, 1965 (Box 2.161, Folder 14)
    - Audit Report, 1966 (Box 2.161, Folder 15)
    - Canadian Certificates, 1983 (Box 2.161, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 2.161, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 2.161, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 2.162, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 2.162, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 3 Feb. 1991 (Box 2.008, Folder 5)
    - Endowment Fund, 1983 (Box 2.162, Folder 3)
    - General, 1991-1993 (Box 2.008, Folder 6)
    - Insurance Records, 1975-1983 (Box 2.162, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, Jul. 1991 (Box 2.008, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, Mar. 1992 (Box 2.008, Folder 8)
    - Meeting, 21-22 Mar. 1992 (Box 2.008, Folder 9)
    - Meeting, 3-4 Apr. 1993 (Box 2.008, Folder 10)
    - Meeting, 11-13 Mar. 1994 (Box 2.008, Folder 11)
    - Meeting, 12-13 Mar. 1994 (Box 2.009, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, 12-13 Mar. 1994 (Box 2.009, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, Spring 1994 (Box 2.009, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, 10-12 Feb. 1995 (Box 2.009, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, Feb. 1996 (Box 2.009, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, 7-9 Feb. 1997 (Box 2.009, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, 28 Feb. 1998 (Box 2.009, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, 20 Feb. 1999 (Box 2.009, Folder 8)
    - Meeting, 11 Mar. 2000 (Box 2.009, Folder 9)
    - Meeting, 10 Mar. 2001 (Box 2.009, Folder 10)
    - Ohio Company Review, 1991-1993 (Box 2.009, Folder 11)
    - Royalty Statements, 1978-1983 (Box 2.162, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Grants-In-Aid of Research
    - Alexander von Humboldt Foundation, 1994-1995 (Box 2.102, Folder 2)
    - American Scientist, 1995 (Box 2.01, Folder 1)
    - Annual Reports, 1972-1991 (Box 2.01, Folder 2)
    - Application Forms, 1992-1994 (Box 2.01, Folder 3)
    - Applications (1), 1966-1970 (Box 2.162, Folder 6)
    - Applications (2), 1966-1970 (Box 2.162, Folder 7)
    - Applications (3), 1966-1970 (Box 2.162, Folder 8)
    - Applications (4), 1966-1970 (Box 2.162, Folder 9)
    - Applications (5), 1966-1970 (Box 2.162, Folder 10)
    - Applications (6), 1966-1970 (Box 2.162, Folder 11)
    - Applications (7), 1966-1970 (Box 2.162, Folder 12)
    - Applications (8), 1966-1970 (Box 2.162, Folder 13)
    - Applications (9), 1966-1970 (Box 2.162, Folder 14)
    - Applications (10), 1966-1970 (Box 2.163, Folder 1)
    - Applications (11), 1966-1970 (Box 2.163, Folder 2)
    - Applications (12), 1966-1970 (Box 2.163, Folder 3)
    - Applications (13), 1966-1970 (Box 2.163, Folder 4)
    - Applications (14), 1966-1970 (Box 2.163, Folder 5)
    - Applications (15), 1966-1970 (Box 2.163, Folder 6)
    - Applications (16), 1966-1970 (Box 2.163, Folder 7)
    - Applications (17), 1966-1970 (Box 2.163, Folder 8)
    - Applications (18), 1966-1970 (Box 2.163, Folder 9)
    - Applications (19), 1966-1970 (Box 2.163, Folder 10)
    - Applications (1), 1971-1975 (Box 2.163, Folder 11)
    - Applications (2), 1971-1975 (Box 2.163, Folder 12)
    - Applications (3), 1971-1975 (Box 2.164, Folder 1)
    - Applications (4), 1971-1975 (Box 2.164, Folder 2)
    - Applications (5), 1971-1975 (Box 2.164, Folder 3)
    - Applications (6), 1971-1975 (Box 2.164, Folder 4)
    - Applications (7), 1971-1975 (Box 2.164, Folder 5)
    - Applications (8), 1971-1975 (Box 2.164, Folder 6)
    - Applications (9), 1971-1975 (Box 2.164, Folder 7)
    - Applications (10), 1971-1975 (Box 2.164, Folder 8)
    - Applications (11), 1971-1975 (Box 2.164, Folder 9)
    - Applications (12), 1971-1975 (Box 2.164, Folder 10)
    - Applications (13), 1971-1975 (Box 2.164, Folder 11)
    - Applications (14), 1971-1975 (Box 2.164, Folder 12)
    - Applications (15), 1971-1975 (Box 2.164, Folder 13)
    - Applications (16), 1971-1975 (Box 2.164, Folder 14)
    - Applications (17), 1971-1975 (Box 2.164, Folder 15)
    - Applications (18), 1971-1975 (Box 2.165, Folder 1)
    - Applications (19), 1971-1975 (Box 2.165, Folder 2)
    - Applications (20), 1971-1975 (Box 2.165, Folder 3)
    - Applications (21), 1971-1975 (Box 2.165, Folder 4)
    - Applications (22), 1971-1975 (Box 2.165, Folder 5)
    - Applications (23), 1971-1975 (Box 2.165, Folder 6)
    - Applications (24), 1971-1975 (Box 2.165, Folder 7)
    - Applications (25), 1971-1975 (Box 2.165, Folder 8)
    - Applications (26), 1971-1975 (Box 2.165, Folder 9)
    - Applications (27), 1971-1975 (Box 2.165, Folder 10)
    - Applications (28), 1971-1975 (Box 2.165, Folder 11)
    - Applications (29), 1971-1975 (Box 2.165, Folder 12)
    - Applications (1), 1976-1980 (Box 2.165, Folder 13)
    - Applications (2), 1976-1980 (Box 2.165, Folder 14)
    - Applications (3), 1976-1980 (Box 2.165, Folder 15)
    - Applications (4), 1976-1980 (Box 2.166, Folder 1)
    - Applications (5), 1976-1980 (Box 2.166, Folder 2)
    - Applications (6), 1976-1980 (Box 2.166, Folder 3)
    - Applications (7), 1976-1980 (Box 2.166, Folder 4)
    - Applications (8), 1976-1980 (Box 2.166, Folder 5)
    - Applications (9), 1976-1980 (Box 2.166, Folder 6)
    - Applications (10), 1976-1980 (Box 2.166, Folder 7)
    - Applications (11), 1976-1980 (Box 2.166, Folder 8)
    - Applications (12), 1976-1980 (Box 2.166, Folder 9)
    - Applications (13), 1976-1980 (Box 2.166, Folder 10)
    - Applications (14), 1976-1980 (Box 2.166, Folder 11)
    - Applications (15), 1976-1980 (Box 2.166, Folder 12)
    - Applications (16), 1976-1980 (Box 2.166, Folder 13)
    - Applications (17), 1976-1980 (Box 2.166, Folder 14)
    - Applications (18), 1976-1980 (Box 2.166, Folder 15)
    - Applications (19), 1976-1980 (Box 2.166, Folder 16)
    - Applications (20), 1976-1980 (Box 2.167, Folder 1)
    - Applications (21), 1976-1980 (Box 2.167, Folder 2)
    - Applications (22), 1976-1980 (Box 2.167, Folder 3)
    - Applications (23), 1976-1980 (Box 2.167, Folder 4)
    - Applications (24), 1976-1980 (Box 2.167, Folder 5)
    - Applications (25), 1976-1980 (Box 2.167, Folder 6)
    - Applications (26), 1976-1980 (Box 2.167, Folder 7)
    - Applications (27), 1976-1980 (Box 2.167, Folder 8)
    - Applications (28), 1976-1980 (Box 2.167, Folder 9)
    - Applications (29), 1976-1980 (Box 2.167, Folder 10)
    - Applications (30), 1976-1980 (Box 2.167, Folder 11)
    - Applications (31), 1976-1980 (Box 2.167, Folder 12)
    - Applications (32), 1976-1980 (Box 2.167, Folder 13)
    - Applications (33), 1976-1980 (Box 2.167, Folder 14)
    - Applications (34), 1976-1980 (Box 2.167, Folder 15)
    - Applications (35), 1976-1980 (Box 2.168, Folder 1)
    - Applications (36), 1976-1980 (Box 2.168, Folder 2)
    - Applications (37), 1976-1980 (Box 2.168, Folder 3)
    - Applications (38), 1976-1980 (Box 2.168, Folder 4)
    - Applications (39), 1976-1980 (Box 2.168, Folder 5)
    - Applications (40), 1976-1980 (Box 2.168, Folder 6)
    - Applications (41), 1976-1980 (Box 2.168, Folder 7)
    - Applications (42), 1976-1980 (Box 2.168, Folder 8)
    - Applications (43), 1976-1980 (Box 2.168, Folder 9)
    - Applications (44), 1976-1980 (Box 2.168, Folder 10)
    - Applications (45), 1976-1980 (Box 2.168, Folder 11)
    - Applications (46), 1976-1980 (Box 2.168, Folder 12)
    - Applications (47), 1976-1980 (Box 2.168, Folder 13)
    - Applications (48), 1976-1980 (Box 2.168, Folder 14)
    - Applications (49), 1976-1980 (Box 2.168, Folder 15)
    - Applications (50), 1976-1980 (Box 2.168, Folder 16)
    - Applications (51), 1976-1980 (Box 2.169, Folder 1)
    - Applications (52), 1976-1980 (Box 2.169, Folder 2)
    - Applications (53), 1976-1980 (Box 2.169, Folder 3)
    - Applications (54), 1976-1980 (Box 2.169, Folder 4)
    - Applications (55), 1976-1980 (Box 2.169, Folder 5)
    - Applications (56), 1976-1980 (Box 2.169, Folder 6)
    - Applications (57), 1976-1980 (Box 2.169, Folder 7)
    - Applications (58), 1976-1980 (Box 2.169, Folder 8)
    - Applications (59), 1976-1980 (Box 2.169, Folder 9)
    - Applications (60), 1976-1980 (Box 2.169, Folder 10)
    - Applications (61), 1976-1980 (Box 2.169, Folder 11)
    - Applications (62), 1976-1980 (Box 2.169, Folder 12)
    - Applications (63), 1976-1980 (Box 2.169, Folder 13)
    - Applications (64), 1976-1980 (Box 2.169, Folder 14)
    - Applications (65), 1976-1980 (Box 2.169, Folder 15)
    - Applications (66), 1976-1980 (Box 2.169, Folder 16)
    - Applications (67), 1976-1980 (Box 2.17, Folder 1)
    - Applications (68), 1976-1980 (Box 2.17, Folder 2)
    - Applications (69), 1976-1980 (Box 2.17, Folder 3)
    - Applications (70), 1976-1980 (Box 2.17, Folder 4)
    - Applications (71), 1976-1980 (Box 2.17, Folder 5)
    - Applications (72), 1976-1980 (Box 2.17, Folder 6)
    - Applications (73), 1976-1980 (Box 2.17, Folder 7)
    - Applications (74), 1976-1980 (Box 2.17, Folder 8)
    - Applications (75), 1976-1980 (Box 2.17, Folder 9)
    - Applications (76), 1976-1980 (Box 2.17, Folder 10)
    - Applications (77), 1976-1980 (Box 2.17, Folder 11)
    - Applications (78), 1976-1980 (Box 2.17, Folder 12)
    - Applications (79), 1976-1980 (Box 2.17, Folder 13)
    - Applications (80), 1976-1980 (Box 2.17, Folder 14)
    - Applications (1), 1981-1985 (Box 2.17, Folder 15)
    - Applications (2), 1981-1985 (Box 2.17, Folder 16)
    - Applications (3), 1981-1985 (Box 2.171, Folder 1)
    - Applications (4), 1981-1985 (Box 2.171, Folder 2)
    - Applications (5), 1981-1985 (Box 2.171, Folder 3)
    - Applications (6), 1981-1985 (Box 2.171, Folder 4)